那个在"第六感"里面的男孩 他最后死了?
So the boy in "The Sixth Sense," he dies at the end?
不 第六感是爱的感觉
No, the sixth sense is love.
-别透剧 -老兄 这电影是十二年前的
-Guys, spoilers. -The movie's 12 years old, bro.
噢 你们肯定不会相信
Oh, you're never gonna believe
今天我在药店碰到谁了
who I ran into today at the drugstore.
一个在买香波的老太太?
An old lady buying shampoo?
-一个在那个店里工作的人? -是的 而且
-A guy who works at the drugstore? -Yes. Also,
菲茨杰拉尔德先生 我最爱的高中老师
Mr. Fitzgerald, my favorite high school teacher.
他酷毙了!
He was the coolest!
他老是让我们叫他"艾伦"
I mean, he used to let us call him "Alan."
戴夫在储物柜里贴了两张照片
Okay, Dave had two pictures in his locker--
内维 坎贝尔 和菲茨杰拉尔德先生
Neve Campbell and Mr. Fitzgerald.
他让我们知道了
-He taught us
连环画也和小说一样有文学性
that comic books were just as literary as novels.
他总是穿着凉鞋来上课
He wore sandals to class.
好吧 又来了 还有他的死亡诗社
Okay, pump the brakes, Dead Poets Society.
他曾给我说过:"戴夫 追寻你的梦想
He used to say to me, "Dave, Chase your dreams.
不要让你的梦想来追你"
Don't let your dreams Chase you."
我们知道了 他触动了（摸了）你
We get it. He touched you.
真的? 这不是你的错 戴夫 这不是你的错
Really? It's not your fault, Dave. Dave, it's not your fault.
别用"心灵捕手"那套
Stop "Good Will Hunting" me.
别再拿我和罗宾 威廉姆斯的电影时代相比了
In fact, stop comparing me to Robin Williams
来呀 开张了
movies period. Come on. It just opened up.
这是在干嘛呢?
What's happening here?
是一家新开张的咖啡店 尼克咖啡与茶 很好
It's a new coffee shop. Nick's coffee&TEA. NICE.
附近的人都可以有个好的喝咖啡的店了
the neighborhood could use a good coffee shop.
这不是一个店而是一个连锁店
It's not a shop. It's a chain.
我们仅在西海岸就开了三百多家
We got over 300 stores on the west coast alone.
阿莱克斯 一家咖啡连锁店
Alex, a coffee chain
就是一个明确的中产阶级标志
is a clear indication of gentrification.
-你知道那意味着什么吗 -南瓜拿铁咖啡
Do you know what that means? Pumpkin lattes, bro.
那意味着我们的房租会涨 意味着有机食品店
it means our rent goes up. It means organic grocery stores.
意味着家庭 戴夫  家庭
It means families, Dave. Families.
刚出炉的脱脂小面包!
Warm buttermilk scones!
阿莱克斯 你们所有人都该把这件事放在心上
Alex, you of all people should be concerned about this.
一家连锁店是头号大敌
A chain store is the number one enemy
对于像你自己这样的小商户来说
of a small business owner like yourself.
你知道吗? 你是对的
-You know what? You're right.
我以前从来没想过这些
I never really thought about that before.
知道吗 我的第一杯咖啡是
You know, the first coffee I ever had
在菲茨杰拉尔德先生的课上
was in Fitzgerald's class.
他让我们讨论名著时喝的
He let us drink it during great books discussions.
好的 让我在这个杯子人身上
Okay, show me on the Cupman
看看他是摸了（触动）你那儿
where he touched you.
幸福终点站
第一季 第09集
==深影字幕组==
-戴夫 这三明治是香蕉口味的 -多谢 彭
-Dave, this sandwich is bananas. -Thanks, Pen.
我只是希望生意能够好起来 知道吗?
I just wish business would pick up, you know?
嗯 成功是需要时间的
-Well, success takes time.
B-52s的漫步也不是一天就写好的
"Roam" by the B-52s wasn't written in a day.
嘿 你知道你知道你该做点什么宣传吗?
Hey you know what you should do for publicity?
就是你该参加汽车食物大赛
Is you should enter that big food truck competition
-他们每年都举办的   - 快餐车比赛?
-that they have every year. -The truckies?
- 是的   -我做的三明治还不是很好
-Yeah.  - My sandwiches aren't flashy enough,
不像那个该死的蚌米货车
not like that damn banh mi truck
和他们那愚蠢美味的 十里飘香的梅奥 嗯
and their stupid delicious, tangy Mayo. Hmm.
怎么可能! 是菲茨杰拉尔德先生
No way! Mr. Fitzgerald!
-叫我艾伦 -艾伦 还是这么兴奋
-Call me Alan. -Alan. Still a thrill.
我真的很高兴你决定过来 当然
I'm so glad you decided to come by. Sure.
你还记得我高中的朋友彭妮  哈茨? 嘿!
Uh, you remember my friend Penny Hartz from high school? Hey!
我怎么会忘记呢?
How I could I forget?
你以前很极端和被人误会
You were so intense and misunderstood.
我以前是 是的
I really was. Yeah.
- 那么...这个是给你的 - 哦?
- So... This is for you. - Oh?
我不知道你是否注意到了这辆老货车
I don't know if you noticed the old truck here,
我正为梦想而努力 你知道 像凯鲁亚克一样
but I'm kind of living my dream. You know, like kerouac.
-我的办公室在公路上  有点傻哈
-My office is on the road. stupid.
-戴夫 这样真的很好 真的 -是吗?
-Dave, this is really good. Really good. -Yeah?
你知道什么能让这个更好吃吗?
You know what would take it to the next level?
拉我在普吉岛修建孤儿院的时候
This si-io KHAO tamerind slaw that I learned to make
我学会做的思域山罗望子卷心菜色拉
when I was building orphanages in Phuket.
-哦!外国菜   - 传说
Ooh! Exotic. Legend has it
当地的人把它当成一种有效的壮阳药
that the locals used it as a powerful aphrodisiac.
愿听其详
Listening.
但如果这个剂量稍稍低一点
But if the measurements are even slightly off,
它就会变成威力强大的利尿剂  啊
it becomes a potent diuretic. Ugh.
噢 不论怎样 我真的觉得这些风味
Ooh. Anyway, I really think that those flavors
会增强牛排的味道
would intensify the taste of this steak.
一款异域的卷心菜色拉可能就是我所需要的
An exotic slaw might be just what I need
-更上层楼的秘诀  -听起来很色拉棒
-to take my sandwich to the next level. -Sounds slaw-some.
我不知道为什么我这样说
I don't know why I said that.
-挺有趣的 -是吗?
That's a great joke. Yeah?
我觉得听上去也很色拉棒！
I think that, uh, you sound slaw-some.
别说了
Stop.
好的
Okay.
我面试了七个竞争这个实习医生岗位的人
I've interviewed, like, seven people for this intern position,
但没有一个人是准备好的
and nobody comes in prepared.
宝贝 你即将和这个人天天在一起工作
Babe, you're gonna have to work with this person every day.
所以别管他们有没有准备 挑些酷的人吧
Forget prepared. Pick someone cool.
哦 是的 好极了
Oh, yeah, great.
我 我还有九个小时就要过最后期限了
I'm--I'm nine hours past the deadline on a project,
但没事 因为我有杰伊 摩尔和我一起配合
but it's all good 'cause I got Jay Mohr with me doing bits.
为什么杰伊 摩尔总是你心目中的酷的代名词
Why is Jay Mohr always your go-to for cool?
布拉德 只有傻瓜才会根据外表来雇佣人
Brad, only idiots hire people based on charm.
那么 我以前的每一个老板都是傻瓜
Then every boss I've ever had's an idiot,
因为我就是一个魅力十足的人
<i>cause I'm all charm, baby.
我是兰斯阿姆斯特朗
I'm Lancecharmstrong.</i>
好了-- -我妈妈被我迷得多喂了一年的奶
Okay-- I'm so charming, my mom breast-fed me for an extra year.
你只是好运
You are just lucky
还好你没被我面试
you have never been up against me for a job,
因为十足的准备永远都比魅力来得强
because prepared beats charm any day of the week.
保留各自的意见
Agree to disagree.
看呐 马克斯把那男的钓到手了
Hold up. Check out Max making gay stuff happen.
- 哇 如果你不介意  - 这是我的号码
Wow. don't mind if you do. Here's my number.
也不是假的
It's not fake either.
我会打电话到这个的
I will call This
然后用一口讨厌的亚洲口音
and use an offensively Asian accent.
- 像一个真的种族歧视者一样  - 不错
Like, a really racist one. Good for you.
- 不管怎么说 我是马克斯 - 我是伊恩
Anyway, I'm Max. Nice. Ian.
- 打给我  - 噢 他需要一个男朋友
Call me. Oh, he needs a boyfriend.
我已经受够了打雷的时候抱着他了
I am tired of holding him during thunderstorms.
我拿到号码了
I got digits!
看来有人得交出手机了
Looks like someone has a reason to get their cell phone
不管你 我不会付钱的
turned back on. I'm not paying for it.
求求你  我没有钱  布莱德
Please? I have no money, Brad.
这像不像泰国的泼水节
Is this not like having the Thai festival of songkran
-发生在你的嘴里? -是的?
-right in your mouth? -Yes?
棒极了
amazing.
这个卷洗菜色拉
This slaw
会毫无疑问的在快餐车大赛中能帮助我
will definitely help me compete at the truckies.
- 我要做这个  - 告诉你
I'm gonna do it. Tell you what.
我到时会来跟你一起做一大份的卷心菜色拉
I'll come by the day of and make a big batch of slaw with you.
你会为我那样做吗?
You would do that for me?
当然 你是我最喜欢的学生
Of course. You were my favorite student.
我就知道  好了 我要把这思域山洗掉
I knew it. All right, I'm gonna go wash thesi-io khao off my hands.
我闻起来像侯尔山
I smell like Koh Kor mountain.
他太酷了
He's so cool.
我知道
I know!
他刚刚是不是说了他闻起来像鸡巴婊子山?
Did he just say he smells like Coke whore mountain?
嘿 反应快点
Hey, quick download.
艾伦约我出去   你同意吗?
Alan asked me out. Is that cool with you?
彭妮  艾伦是我生命的很重要的一部分
Penny, Alan was a huge part of my life.
我们放学后会花几个小时在一起
We spent hours Together after school.
他教我..是的
He taught me... Yeah.
关于书 艺术 还有爱情 但是他没碰我
About books, art, and love... But he didn't touch me.
但是他总是为我守候
But he was always there for me.
呃...真的不知道我得到的指令是什么
So... not really clear what my marching orders are.
我能和他一起出去吗?
Can I got out with him?
只要  如果你想要
Only... if you wanna do
做世界上最棒的事情
the most awesome thing in the world.
那就是说你同意了?
Is that a "Yes"?
是的! 是的! 我只是尽量的在跟上
Yes! Yes! I'm just trying to follow.
好的 太棒了!
Okay, yes!
那么当男同志们勾搭的时候
So when gay guys hook up,
他们会称呼对方"兄弟"吗?
do they call each other "Dude"?
比如说"兄弟 你的唇真的很柔软"
Like, "Dude, your lips are so soft"?
或者"你的胡须好痒，小狗狗"
Or "Your mustache is ticklin' my navel, dawg"?
你是一个白痴 但是 是的 我们会那样
You're an idiot. But, yeah, we do that.
我就知道!
I knew it!
马克斯! 嘿 马克斯 你非常正确
Max! Hey, Max, you were so right.
那个 尼克的连锁店真的是一个威胁
Okay, Nick's is a real threat
他们早已经从三家当地的咖啡店里
They've already hired Baristas away
挖走了咖啡员工
from Three local coffee shops.
所以我同一些当地的个体户谈过了 我们要
So I talked to some local small business owners. We are gonna
在明天晚上会面来商讨一个行动的计划
meet tomorrow Night and Come up with a plan of action.
好吧 我是这次战斗的代理 !  噢!
Okay, I am gonna be an Agent of CHAOS! Ooh!
我还找了几家柠檬吧 来吧  马克斯 哦!
And I'm bringing Lemon bars. Come on, Max. Ooh!
哦 你--你可以成为我的同性恋格瓦拉
Oh, you--you could be my gay Guevara.
讨厌那个绰号 出于对柠檬吧的兴趣 我加入
Hate that nickname, addicted to Lemon bars. I'm in.
走吧 你这个大忙人 我们一定能把他们搬倒
Let's go, you little munchkin. We are going to take them down!
因此我找到了一个方法
So I figured out a way
来弄清谁能在面试中发挥的更好
to find out who's better at interviews.
我们俩都去参加那个咖啡店的面试
We both interview at that coffee shop.
亚历克斯说过他们会雇佣 在面试中成功的人
Alex said they're hiring. Whoever gets the job wins.
-像往常一样赌吗? -我参加 往常一样赌
-Usual bet? -I'm in. Usual bet.
没人在乎小角色
No one cares about the little guy.
那家连锁店快逼死我了 嗯
The chain hardware stores are killin' me. Mm-hmm.
我的业绩也下降了百分之四十 是的
My business is down 40%. Yeah.
斯科特 我认为造成那样结果的一部分原因是
Scott, I think part of that has something to do with the fact
你因为卖海豚肉被捕事 哦 斯科特
that you got caught selling dolphin meat. Oh, Scott.
好吧 嗯 我们要采取怎样的行动?
All right, Well,?what are we gonna do about it?
我们要杀了他们然后卖他们的肉 !
We kill them! Sell their meat!
告诉人们那只是金枪鱼肉!
Tell people It's tuna!
斯科特 我 我欣赏你的热情
Scott, I-I love your enthusiasm,
但是 你知道... 嗯!
but, you know... mm!
我们应该从小处着手  你知道的?
Maybe We should start small, you know?
比如说  请愿书怎么样?
Like, what about a petition?
我故意的
I meant to do that.
好了 我不是故意的 但是我很高兴它发生了
Okay, I didn't mean to do that, but I'm glad it happened.
请愿书? 我是说 我们在这儿讨论什么呢?
A petition? I mean, what are we talking about here?
那 你有更好的主意吗?
Well, do you have a better idea?
我好主意多的是
I got about a thousand better ideas.
搞抗议我经验足足的
拯救韦斯特菲尔德的邋遢乔
Save the Sloppy Joes at Westfield!
我们要这么干 都靠过来
Here's what we're gonna do. Bring it in.
好的 挤拢一点
Okay. Get real tight.
啊 嗯 每个人都单膝跪下 第一排的 跪下
Mm-hmm. Everybody, take a knee. Front row, take a knee.
靠拢 马克斯 很抱歉妨碍你
Real tight. Max, I'm sorry to bother you.
我不得不换另一条腿
I'm gonna need to take another knee.
两条腿都跪下 斯科特
Take both knees, Scotty.
好了 这就是我认为我们应该--我只是觉得
Okay, here's what I think we should--I just feel like
我们挤得不够紧  我们没有挤在一起
we're not tight in this space. We're not tight
够挤了，你到底什么主意?
in here. We're tight! What's the idea?
你觉得卡皮沙巴怎么样?
How do you like the moqueca capixaba?
哦 如果就是这东西的话 我很喜欢
Oh. If that this is thing, I like it very much.
嗯 很好 你去过如此多迷人的地方
Oh. Great. You have been to so many glamorous places.
-为什么还要回到这儿来呢? -嗯 现在
-Why would you come back here? -Well, right now,
我正在尽力做我的四桶竞技场
I'm working my way through four bucket lists,
这件事让我有点经济紧张
and It's left me a little strapped for cash,
因此我不得不和我的妹妹
so I gotta crash with my sister
还有他愚蠢的丈夫麦克住在一起
and her dumb husband Mike,
一个成功的税务律师
the successful tax attorney.
就像这样 "麦克 如果你不喜欢客人
It's like, "Mike, if you don't want guests,
就别建客房 你个蠢货"
don't build a guesthouse, you idiot."
嗯
mmm.
你知道 你的到来让戴夫有多激动
You know, Dave is just so excited that you're here.
我是说你真的给了他很多的灵感
I mean, you really inspired him.
嗯 是的 这就是我的好处
Mm. Yeah, that's my jam.
艾伦 菲茨杰拉尔德是一个给人指引别人的人
Alan Fitzgerald-- mind shaper.
戴夫 雷诺兹一直是我最喜欢的学生之一
And Dave Reynolds has always been one of my favorites.
戴夫 罗斯 -戴夫 雷诺兹
Dave Rose. -Dave Rhodes.
罗斯 你懂...
<i>Rose.You know...
我刚才就是这么读的 雷诺兹
that's what I'm saying. Rhodes.</i>
罗斯-罗斯-罗斯 -雷诺兹 你说的雷诺兹
<i>Rose. -Rose. -Rose. -Rhodes. You say it. Rhodes.</i>
对了 我们读的一样 -不 不 不一样
Yeah, we're saying the same thing. -No. No, we're not.
打扰了!-什么事 先生?
Excuse me! -Yes, sir?
嘿 再来一瓶马尔贝克酒好吗?
Hi. Can I get another bottle of Malbec, please?
好 -谢谢
Okay. -Thanks.
顺便说一句 我没带钱
by the way, I don't have any money,
但是我会写诗给你作为偿还 砰
but I'm gonna pay you back in poems. Boom.
酷  -那个女孩挺可爱
Cool. That girl's cute.
那是你男朋友? - 那是她老公 我认为
Is that your boyfriend? -It's her husband, I think.
什么? 哦 我的错
Excuse me? Oh, my fault.
那么...艾伦到底有多酷?
So... How cool is Alan?
哦...非常酷
<i>Oh...so cool.</i>
就像 呃 我要一件夹克衫!
Like, brr, I need a jacket!
我知道!他约会的时候是什么样子?
I knew it! What's he like on a date?
比方说 在他吻你之前他会说什么?
Like, what did he say to you right before he kissed you?
是不是惊天地泣鬼神? -哦...对
Was it the best line ever? -Ohh... Yeah.
他说
He said,
"我有责任 让你嗨起来"
"I have the need, the need for speed."
那...
That...
真是...
is so...
棒极了! -什么? 怎么?
awesome! -What? I what?
哦 我的天! 我太为你高兴了!
Oh, my god! I'm so happy for you!
哦 哦! 这个人 可能就是你的真命天子!
Oh. Oh! This guy, he might be the one!
penny做的指头交叉的动作是美国人祈求上天保佑时候的手势
嘿 谢谢你陪我去班
Hey, thanks for walking me to work.
让我看起来不那么囧 -呃 我是个绅士
Saved me from the walk of shame. -Well, I am a gentleman.
另外 我也需要买洗发水
Plus, I need to get some shampoo.
我已经用洗手液洗头
I've been washing my hair with hand sanitizer
三个星期了 -哦 嗯...性感
for the past three weeks. -Yeah, well... sexy.
我到了 -哦 你在这儿工作
This is me. -Oh. You work here.
不是 呃 实际上...
Not really. Uh, actually...
很好 这地方只是...
good, 'cause this place just...
我是老板 -那我真心想进去享受一番
I'm the owner. -One place I really wanna go in and enjoy.
那么你...拥有这块地方意味着你...
So you... own this place in the sense that you, like...
买下它了?
own it?
我投入了我所有的存款-哦
Put All my savings into it. -Oh.
行情不好
It sucks, though.
本地同行好像不那么欢迎我
The local businesses are not exactly welcoming.
他们已经开始发传单 想发起抵制活动
They've been passing out flyers, trying to organize a boycott.
我甚至觉得他们就是骚扰我表哥蒂姆的那伙人
I even think they're the ones who harassed my cousin Tim.
嘿 伙计
Hey, man.
我们不喜欢你在这转来转去 -什么?
We don't like your kind 'round here. -What?
别太紧张 放松点 好吗?
<i>Not so Grande now, are you,ese?</i>
喔 喔 喔! -斯科特?!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! -Scott?!
别说出我的名字! -斯科特 你在干嘛?!
don't say my name! Scott, what are you doing?!
我的名字不是斯科特 -啊!
my name's not Scott. Aah!
他缩进去了!-他缩进去了!他缩进去了!
He's turtling! He's turtling! He's turtling!
啊!啊!啊!
Aah! Aah!
我不叫斯科特!
my name's not Scott!
你就不该叫我的名字
You shouldn't have said my name.
你为什么会拿把弹簧刀?!
Why do you have a switchblade?!
因为我没找到我的枪
<i>because I couldn't find mygun.</i>
真可怕
Weird.
事实证明 戴夫的英雄 菲茨杰拉尔德先生
So it turns out, Dave's hero, Mr. Fitzgerald,
是个不折不扣的酒鬼 可是戴夫却不明白
is a full-on douche, and Dave can't see it.
彭妮!
Penny!
我不能没有你!我要让所有人都知道!
I can't live without you! I want everybody to know!
艾伦!我说过我再也不想跟你一起出去了
Alan! I told you I don't want to go out with you again.
等等 等等 等等 等等 等等 等等
Wait, Wait, Wait, Wait, Wait, wait, wait.
我为你写了首诗
I wrote you a poem.
我把它叫做...
It's called...
"你能给我个碳烤奶酪三明治吗?"
"Can you make me a grilled cheese sandwich?"
你喝醉了?才上午10点
Are you drunk? It's 10:00 a.M.
等下! 等下! 等下!
Hold on! hold on! hold on!
我要跟你说件非常重要的事
I need to speak with you about something very important.
好 什么事? -到底怎么了?
Okay. What? -What's up?
哦 艾伦 从我的走廊上滚出去
<i>Oh, Alan, get out of my hallway.
你 滚出我的走廊!
You leave my hallway!</i>
嘿 我们一起走!跟我一起去马达加斯加
<i>Hey,you leave the hallway! And come with me to Madagascar.</i>
不 快走
No. Right now.
不!你该醒醒了
no! You need to sober up
接着去为戴夫做卷心菜色拉 好吗?
and get to work on that slaw for Dave, okay?
快餐车赛四小时后就要开始了
<i>The truckies are in four hours.
去他的快餐车!
Truck the truckies!</i>
现在说的是我俩  在一起
This is about me and you hanging out,
你还可以给我开张支票，1000块最好
and you writing me a check for, like, a Grand tops.
没关系 谁在乎别人怎么想?
Besides, who cares about anybody else?
戴夫 在乎 好吗
Dave cares, okay.
他太关注你和你的想法了
He cares so much about you and your opinion.
好吧 很显然 你很关心这个叫戴夫的
Okay. Obviously, you're very concerned about this Dave guy.
对 -我想让你知道我
Yeah. -I want you to know that I am...
我们可以3P
totally open to a 3-way.
噢 天呐
Oh, my god.
撞到了我的鸡鸡
That was my penis.
戴夫对这家伙盲目的追随
Dave has always had a blind spot for that guy.
我不喜欢他 我不信任老师
I don't like him. I do not trust teachers
尤其是不愿发成绩单的老师
who refuse to give out letter grades.
我是说 我懂了 我们都是祖国的花朵
I mean, I get it. We're all snowflakes,
但我们中的一些
but some of us are
是更好，更聪明的花朵
better, smarter snowflakes who studied for the test.
她就是那种女孩 我知道
<i>She was that girl in high school. I know.</i>
为了这个重要的面试
So I got my resume all laminated and updated
我把我的简历更新还裹了塑-这是我的简历
<i>for the big interview. -This is my resume
开些玩笑 比方说"你被P90X击中了吗"
Couple of jokes, couple of "You been hittin' the P90X?"
当他说不懂P90X是什么的时候 我就会说
Then when he doesn't know what the P90x is, I'm like,
"老兄 你现在就被击中了"
<i>"Bro, you gotta hit the P90X now."</i>
然后套套近乎 就得到了这份工作
Then just some dude stuff, then I get the job.
哦 真的吗?
Oh, really?
是 -你能告诉我这四种豆子的区别吗?
Yep. Can you tell the difference between all four of these beans?
它们差别可大了去了- 都是做咖啡的
'cause they could not be more different. -They are all coffee.
这么说的话 它们更应该不同
<i>So in that sense, they could be more different.</i>
这就是魅力所在  - 那你会雇佣谁?
Yeah. Who would you hire? That's the charm right there.
噢!我才不在乎
Ooh! I don't care.
嘿 阿莱 我能跟你说句话吗?
Hey, Al. Could I talk to you for a second?
马克斯 你为抗议活动做好准备了吗?
Max, you ready for the protest?
是的 充分准备好了 关于抗议-
Yeah. Totally. About that-
我们把它取消然后去看电影
let's cancel it and go see a movie.
彼得.特拉弗斯告诉我有一部新上映的
There's a new one out that Peter Travers says
叫做"密室逃脱"
is a "Stage 5 thrill-icane."
认真点 我们得出发了
-Let's get serious. We gotta go.
事实上 我已经做了大量调查
Actually, I've also been doing a ton of research,
结果显示
and it turns out
那家尼克咖啡厅是个非常不错的公司
that Nick's coffee is a super cool company,
不过我以前不知道
which I did not know,
他们资助非洲儿童大量物资
and they give a ton of money to African kids
而且他们还把难民接到博卡
and they're, like, flying out all these refugees to Boca--
好吧 你彻底把我打败了
All right, you beat it out of me.
我正在和那家的店主约会 他真的很酷
I'm dating the owner Ian. He's so cool.
我正处在一个典型的男性困境
I'm in a serious "You've got male" situation--
"男人"拼做"男" "人"
"Male" Spelled m-a-l-e.
真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我知道这就像是让人困惑的文字游戏
I know. It's dazzling wordplay.
我就是彼得.特拉弗斯
I'm the Peter Travers
在男同性恋关系中挣扎
of complicated gay relationships.
我还是个叛徒 - 你知道..我也是个叛徒
I'm also a sellout. -Well, you know... I'm a sellout, too.
你看见这些标语了吗?
You see these signs?
我从一些官员那儿拿到这些广告板
I got the poster boards at office plus.
这些价格贵的离谱! -我知道
The prices are unreal!  -I know.
那么你不会生我的气?-不!你就像个小男孩
So you're not mad at me? -No! You like a boy.
那是叛徒最滑稽的地方
That is totally the funnest thing to sell out for.
你是最棒的-你就像个小男孩!你就像个小男孩!
You're the best. -you like a boy! You like a boy!
现在你这么快就变成最坏的了
and now you're the worst very quickly.
好的 嗯 我们现在就终止抗议
Okay, Well, we have to stop this protest
把时间都省给爱
and save the day for love.
哇 哇 哇 我从没说过是爱
Whoa, whoa, whoa. I never said anything about love.
得了 为了爱 为了爱
Come on. For love! For love!
为了喜欢 为了喜欢!
For like.Like!
怎么了 戴夫?-嘿!
What up, Dave? -Hey!
腌泡汁闻起来不错
That marinade smells amazing.
我们迫不及待的看你去赢了 -我这就去
We're all so psyched to see you kick ass at the truckies. -I'm almost ready to go.
我就是在等一会艾伦来为我做卷心菜色拉
I'm just waiting on Alan to get here to make the slaw.
这没什么大不了的
But it's no big deal.
他只迟到了半小时 但是..
He's just a few half-hours late, but...
戴夫 我想让你知道...
Dave, I just want you to know...
你做的三明治
you've got a really great sandwich
即使不配沙拉也是美味
with or without that slaw.
马上就有卷心菜色拉了 为什么没有了?
There's gonna be slaw. Why wouldn't there be slaw?
我想说的是 艾伦今天可能不会来了
What I'm trying to say is, Alan might not come today
因为他可能没你想想的那么完美
because he may not be as great of a guy as you think he is.
彭妮 我知道你想说什么
Penny, I know what you're doing.
好吧 我和艾伦谈过了
All right, I talked to Alan.
你很受伤因为你刚刚和他分手 -什么?
You're just hurt because he broke it off with you. -What?
是的 想我和他这样的人思想很自由
Yeah, guys like me and him are free spirits.
你知道 我们任思想漫游
You know, we gotta be free to roam.
我们自由自在的...
We gotta be free to...
那真是见鬼了 我发誓我再也不会这么做
<i>That is so weird. I promise I will never do that again.</i>
戴夫你跟艾伦不同 好不好?
Dave, you are nothing like Alan, okay?
他是个酒鬼 身无分文 还是个蠢货
He's a douche who's broke, and he's stupid
因为他不知道你到底有多棒
because he doesn't realize how awesome you are.
他知道我有多优秀 好吗?
<i>He does realize how awesome I am, okay?</i>
他肯定会来的
And he's gonna be at the truckies.
如果这对你很难接受的话 那你可以不用来了
And if that's too weird for you, then maybe you shouldn't come.
喔 你宁愿他站在这儿而不是我?
Wow. You'd rather have him there than me?
不 彭 只是..色拉在他手上
No. Pen. It's just... he's bringing the slaw.
嘿 菲茨杰先生--艾伦!
Hey, Mr. Fitzg--Alan!
我不想打扰你做事
Don't want to tie you down,
我只是来确认沙拉的事
but I'm just calling to check on the slaw.
嗯 我现在要去准备了
Um, I'm gonna go set up,
但是我会把这些东西都留给你
but I'm gonna leave everything here for you,
你可以自己进来做些你喜欢的东西
and you can just let yourself in and do your thang.
真希望能见到你 好的 爱你
Really hope to see ya, all right. Love ya.
嗯--不 只是--想你
Just--no, that--miss ya.
你知道吗?你加油就行
You know what? You just keep on truckin'.
好了 凯文和斯蒂文
Okay, Kevin and Steve,
你们都是工商管理硕士 真的非常让人惊讶
you both have MBAs. That's really impressive.
布拉德 嗯 你没有提交简历
Brad. Uh, you didn't hand in a résumé.
是有什么原因吗? 这...
Any reason for that? This...
嗯
hmm.
嗯 我脸上有什么东西吗?
Uh, do I have something on my face?
我的简历是--
Here's my résumé--
你和我 咱们可以一起去吃牛排
you, me, couple of steaks,
或者看（NBA）公牛的比赛
bulls game.
-还是去打打棒球吗? -我可以理解成
-I don't know. Batting cages? -So I'm gonna take that as a "No."
你没有带纸制简历
You don't have a paper résumé.
这是我的简历 一式三份
Here is my réSumé in triplicate.
都给你
Take them all.
现在 我们是不是要比赛下
Now is there gonna be a competition
闻咖啡豆辨产地?
where We need to smell the beans and guess where they're from?
-我有带眼罩哦 -我不明白你在说什么
-'cause I brought my own blindfold. -I don't know what that means.
或许我应该面试你下 两部分
You know, maybe I should interview you. 2-parter.
第一 在接下来的五年你有什么目标?
One, where do you see yourself in five years?
第二 我怎么才能帮你完成你的目标?
Two, how did I help you get there?
开始闻咖啡豆比赛时 告诉我就是了
So just let me know when it's time to smell the beans.
这就是你说的眼罩哈
And there's the blindfold you were talking about.
你看起来好个性啊 伙计们 或许你们两
You look fantastic. Guys, maybe you two
-并不适合我公司 -我明白你为什么这样说
-aren't right for this company. -I understand where you're coming from.
但是我很好奇的是
But Riddle me this. Uh...
你喜欢喝什么口味的咖啡啊?
how do you like your coffee, huh?
热的?
Hot?
有点黏糊糊的?
Little sticky?
嗯 黏糊糊的?
Um, sticky?
真的吗 有备而来小姐?
Really, miss preparation?
在小组面试时打性感牌?
Playing the sex card in a group interview?
还有  我是同性恋
Also, I'm gay.
哦!
Ooh!
你知道嘛 我刚刚发现我对咖啡超级
You see, I just find coffee so...
有感觉哦
Sensual.
嗯
Mmm.
-打到连锁店! 打到连锁店! -哇
-Break the chain! Break the chain! -Wow.
打到连锁店! 打到连锁店! 打到连锁店!
Break the chain! Break the chain! Break the chain!
-大声点! -快来 瑞奇! 到这儿来!
-LOUDER! -Come on, Ricky! Get in here!
马克斯!
Max!
我不能让伊恩看见我 你能自己摆平吗?
I can't let Ian see me. Can you stop this by yourself?
好的 我这就去
All right, I got this.
打到连锁店! 打到连锁店!
Break the chain! Break the chain!
打到连锁店! 打到连锁店! 打到连锁店!
Break the chain! Break the chain! Break the chain!
嘿 伙计们! 伙计们 听着!
Hey, guys! Guys, guys, listen up!
听好了 大家 听我说几句
Listen up, everyone. Listen to this.
-我刚接到尼克本人的电话... -什么?
-I actually just got a call from Nick himself... -what?
他真是个好的人
And he's actually a pretty cool guy.
因为他每卖的一杯咖啡
For every cup of coffee he sells,
就会给贫困儿童捐一杯
he gives a cup of coffee to a child in need.
他给孩子们喝咖啡? 脱因咖啡!
He gives coffee to kids? Decaf!
那 你们觉得
So what do you say
我们能不能就此罢手或去看场电影?
we just cancel this thing and go catch a movie?
我意思是...
I mean...
等会  她被收买了  -什么?
-wait a minute. She's been compromised. -What?
把她轰走! 我们选择暴力!
Let's get rid of her! Violence is an option!
什么?什么?哇!啊!
What?What?Wow! Ow!
我们选择暴力! 我们选择暴力!
Violence is an option! Violence is an option!
我不是他们一伙的!你们这么做有些过头了!
I'm not part of it! You guys are crazy!
我们选择暴力! 我们选择暴力!
Violence is an option! Violence is an option!
别这样 不要选择暴力
Stop this. Violence is not an option.
暴力不是什么好的选择 先把这些标语牌放下
Violence is not an option. Let's just put these down.
-见到你们真是很高兴 -哦 嘿
-Meeting you guys was the best. -Oh, Hey, uh,
我有说过你的嘴唇看起来超软嘛 哥们儿?
did I mention your lips look super soft, bro?
有 大概5次吧
-Yeah, about five times.
好吧 假如有人用枪指着你的脑袋问你-
Okay, gun to your head-
你到底要雇谁?
who would you hire?
呃 我会聘请那个拿枪指着你们俩头的人
Uh, the guy with the gun over both of you.
把标语牌放下吧 今天到此为止
Put the signs down, call it a day.
冷静的头脑才是制胜的法宝 回家去吧?
Cooler heads have prevailed. Let's go home, huh?
哦 老天爷 怎么回事?
-Oh, god. What is happening?
好了 大家互相拍拍肩膀回家吧
Okay, so let's Pat ourselves on the back and just go home.
-马克斯? -怎么啦?
Max? -What?
这怎么回事? 你和他们一伙的吗?
What is going on? Are you a part of all this?
和他们一伙的? 马克斯组织我们来的
Pfft. Part of all this? Max started this.
我没有 我和他们没一点关系
I did not start it. I had nothing to do with it.
噢 天啊 我认得这声音
Oh, my god. I-I-I know those voices.
又来了!
Its happening again!
当心! 他俩中有一个有弹簧刀!
Careful! One of them has a switchblade!
他这样躲在下面叫缩头乌龟
It's called turtling, when he goes under like that.
-你打了蒂姆? -哦 这不公平
-You beat up Tim? -Whoa, Whoa, whoa, whoa. That's not fair.
你不能把功劳全归在你自己名下了
You don't take all the credit for this.
是我们一起揍的蒂姆   -好了  斯科特
We beat up Tim together. Okay, Scotty.
马克斯? 阿莱克斯?你们在这干嘛? 嘿！
Max? Alex? What are you guys doing here? Hey!
你们当然是这两个变态的朋友了
Of course you guys are friends with these two perverts.
愿意跟你多呆一会的变态
Perverts who are willing to go the extra mile. Mm.
这全是误会
This is all a misunderstanding.
借过! 借过!
Excuse me! Excuse me!
抱歉 我来晚了
Sorry I'm late!
但我把艾伦的卷心菜沙拉带来了
But I brought Alan's slaw.
真的? -他其实是想自己拿过来的
You did? -He wanted to bring it himself,
但突然有通电话找他
but he got an emergency call,
他就不得不乘第一班航班去普吉岛了
and he had to hop the first flight to Phuket.
我知道你在骗我
I know you're lying.
到这儿之前我去找过艾伦
I went looking for Alan on my way to the truckies.
哦 对了 餐车大赛 我差点忘了
Oh, yeah. The truckies. I almost forgot.
你知道还有什么比那个比赛更有意思的吗?
You know what would be cooler than that?
咱俩开我的货车去
Is if we got in my Van and we drove out to that place
四个州交界的地方
where all four states touch,
同时吸四个地方产的大麻!
and we smoke hella weed in all four at the same time!
嘿 你要是出去的话
Hey, if you're going out,
给我买包创可贴回来好吗?
can you pick me up some band-aids?
我刮腋毛的时候把自己弄破了
I cut my armpit shaving.
他居然叫我戴夫 雷诺兹
And he called me Dave Reynolds.
你记得那家伙嘛 他靠舔东西赚钱的
You remember Dave Reynolds. He used to lick stuff for money.
彭妮 我真觉得自己很蠢
Penny, I-I feel really stupid.
不 我很理解你想要一个偶像的心情
No, I understand wanting to have someone to look up to.
嗯 可能知道现在我才明白
Yeah, well, maybe it's time I realized
我的生活中已经有人在不停的激励我了
that I have people in my life to inspire me.
你是说斯科特 皮彭（NBA球星）吗?
Are you talking about Scottie Pippen?
当然
Always.
另外 原来我不需要艾伦的卷心菜沙拉...
Besides, turns out I didn't need Alan's slaw...
因为我已经赢了!
because I won!
我早和你说过的! 真是太棒了!
I told you! That this awesome!
哦 天啊 真为你感到骄傲
Yeah. Oh, my god. I'm proud of you.
谢谢 瞧我知道这色拉已经是没什么意义了
Thanks. Well, look, I know the slaw is largely a metaphor
现在 但是它还是有用处的
at this point, but maybe you can still use it.
对 没错 这沙拉会很配 --闻起来真恶心
Yeah. Totally. This'll go great on--that smells disgusting.
我给你拿了些香辣炸鸡
I brought you some white Chicken chili Fries.
-韩式料理哦 -我不饿
-Made by Koreans. -I'm not hungry.
哦 别这样 不要再想伊恩了
Oh, come on, screw Ian.
一个把我们仨都
-A guy who turns down all three of us
绝之门外的家伙注定没有什么眼光
clearly cannot recognize a good thing.
-怎么了 满脸烦恼的 -哦 伤心哥!
-What's the matter, fussy face? -Oh, Mr. Sad face!
-他心碎了 -不 我没有 我什么都不在乎
-He got a case of the broken hearts. -No, I don't. I don't care about anything.
现在让我跑一英里都没问题
I could run a mile right now.
不管怎样伊恩还是很性感的
Ian was pretty cute, though.
我打赌他的嘴唇一定像看起来那样柔软
I bet those lips were as soft as they looked.
对啊 我真的不恨他
They were, and I really, really didn't hate him.
好 那 我们去找他
Okay, so... Let's go and get him.
对 我的一位导师曾说过
Yeah, a mentor of mine once said,
"戴夫 追逐梦想 但不要让梦想去追你"
"Dave, Chase your dreams. Don't let your dreams Chase you."
那个导师还说过让我们3p呢 所以别太在意
The same mentor also suggested we have a 3-way so Let's take it
就暂且有所保留吧
with a grain of salt.
好了  就这样办 伙计们!  出发吧!
Okay, let's do this. Come on, guys! Okay, let's go!
我们这就去找他! 为了爱!
Let's go get him! For love!
为了爱! 走 为了爱!
-For love! Come on. For love! Let's go.
伊恩!
IAN!
Ian!
伊恩 我知道你不欢迎我进去
Ian, I know, I'm probably not welcome inside,
如果可以的话我就站在这里喊了
so I'm just gonna yell from here, if that's cool.
好吧
Cool.
听着 和你约会不是什么阴谋诡计
Look, dating you was not part of some weird scheme or plan.
我很抱歉 我把一切都搞砸了
I-I'm sorry I screwed it all up.
我是说 我只是一个站在餐车上的男人
I mean, I'm just a guy standing in a food truck,
我知道这一切令人很费解
which I know is confusing
可能以后我会向你解释 我不知道
and I will explain later maybe. I don't know.
我只不过是站在另一个男人面前的男人...
I'm just a guy standing in front of another guy...
此为电影《诺丁山》里的经典台词
MAX把原句的girl改成了guy
刚意识到这种道歉方式真很奇怪
realizing this is a weird way to handle this.
我只是想本本分分做生意而已
And I'm just a guy trying to run an honest business,
也许能在经济不景气的时候
maybe create some job opportunities
-为大家提供一些工作机会 -那我就是一个
-in a pretty rough economic climate. -And I'm just a guy
在经济危机中挣扎的人
that thrives in a shadow black market economy,
但我很佩服你所做的一切
but I respect everything you're doing.
我也只是一个男人，站在另一个男人面前
I'm also just a guy standing in front of a guy,
希望我们能重归于好
who wishes we could go back to just talking about us.
我是一个正在聆听的男人
I'm a guy who's listening.
还是那个
I am also a guy
被自己的员工们看着，心里怪怪的
who feels pretty weird in front of my employees right now.
嗯哈基姆 你能不能回去
So, uh, Hakeem, if you would be a guy who would go inside
-看好柜台 那最好 -好的
-and maybe watch the register, that'd be great. -You got it, Ian.
谢谢  哈基姆
Thanks, Hakeem.
我还是那个打从心眼里乐意你回来的人
And I'm also a guy who's really glad you came back.
我也是那种喜欢随心所欲
I'm also... kind of a guy who likes to keep things loose.
不想被束缚
You know, don't want to be tied down.
我也喜欢那样 -那好
I could be into that. -That's cool. Yeah, I
我只是不想被束缚而已
just don't want to get locked down or anything.
-对 说得好 -你明白就好 -回见
Yeah, yeah, right. Good game. -Yeah, you get it. -Yeah, see ya around.
噢! 耶!
Oh! Yay!
碰拳问候? 真的吗?  真是碰拳问候?
Fist Bump? Really? A fist Bump?
来吧
Come on.
耶! 哈!
Yeah! Ahh!
走! 成功了  成功了
Go, Blum! Get it. Get it. Get it.
耶
Yeah!
去买百吉饼吧
Let's go get a bagel.
宝贝 我的三明治呢
Where's my sandwich, babe?
呵呵
Mm-hmm.
一定很好吃
Oh, this is gonna taste so good.
把三文治给我
Give me the sandwich.
所以他俩打赌都输了就是这样？
So this is what happens when they both lose the usual bet?
你想知道吗? 我想要背部按摩
You know what? I want a backrub, snooch.
呵 我也想 外加一个圣代
Mm-hmm. Me, too. And a sundae.
狗狗
Puppy.
小丑性爱 嗯! 小丑性爱 嗯!
Clown sex. Mm! Clown sex. Mm!
走! 好
Get over here! Okay.
他俩一点都不在乎我们也在这儿吗?
Did they even care that we're here?
你和伊恩怎么样了?
So how it's going with Ian?
嗯 不怎么样 他已经是三个小孩的爸爸了
Mm, not so good. He's married with three kids.
我明白你的感受 -对啊
Been there. -Yeah.